https://filtertechs.com/privacy-policy/

Home / Privacy Policy
Who we are
FilterTechs Inc.
( Authorized dealer of Lawrence Factor products )1833 S Dixie Hwy Pompano Beach, Florida 33060 USA Our website address is: http://www.filtertechs.com.
How we use your personal data
We DO NOT share your personal contact details with any third party companies. You WILL NOT receive unsolicited advertising emails or phone calls. Our emails or phone support will be for purchase confirmation, updates and delivery details on your order.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
User Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
If you are using a personal picture or avatar image in relation to your email account, an anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. If you have no image associated with your email then the privacy policy below is not applicable to your usage of the website. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. This information can be kept indefinitely unless a request to delete the profile is received. Accounts that are inactive for more than 4 years may be deleted at the discretion of FilterTechsInc.
All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Analytics
Product categoriesAir Filters
Air Testing
Compressor Parts
Filter Towers
Oil & Media
Spare Parts
Uncategorized
Search for:
